ubers.org 2013-06-03

# Uber Forums - Help Documents

**Our privacy policy.**

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we collect, and the ways in which we use that personal information.

**Personal Information Collection**

We may collect following kinds of personal information:

* IP Address.
* Email Address (only required and collected if you sign up or register on this website).
* Any other information that you send us. For example when contacting us through the contact form, we may use the name you entered to address you and reach out to the email address you specified for answering and solving your concerns or issues, if any.

**Using The Personal Information**

As we claimed above discussing the various ways we collect information from our visitors or our site members, we shall now see as to how we do use the personal information that we collect.

Uber Forums, certainly does not disclose any of the information that we collect (as listed above) to either any of the public or private places unless the law enforces us to do so. In such cases, we may supply the legal authorities the data we collected including but not limited to IP address, country, email.

Other than that, our forum software may use the email address to either send electronic newsletter, sending a verification email upon registering an account on this website, Private Message or any thread subscription notification to which you may have subscribed to for further updates (of which both could be disabled and editable via the profile editing settings). Also we do not use any third party sites for delivering such email notifications or newsletter and those emails are automatic and ONLY sent via our own website. In addition to that, we may use the information in ways like collecting a ratio of certain people visiting this website; for example, based upon your birth date (if provided) we may use it to calculate census of how many people on this website belong to 18-24 years, number of male or females or teenagers (between age of 13-18) visiting this website to supply to potential advertisers who are willing to advertise or market their products on a specific sex category or as per the age and likewise.

**Cross-border data transfers**

* Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
* Additionally, personal information that you submit for publication (that is made for public use) on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world including but not limited to posts, threads or topics, your opinions or feedback.
* You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are information packets sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

**How We Use Cookies**

This website may store cookies on your computers for certain general aspects such as but not limited to saving your preferred preferences that you select every time you visit this site, the specific cookies which ARE required in order for this site to function. You can read more about how this website stores the cookie [here](http://www.ubers.org/misc.php?action=help&hid=3). Additionally for certain area, the site may store cookies such as if you are logging as a member, the remember me option (check box) would remember your session to this site and would log you automatically every time you visit this website; that also is YOUR OWN preference whether to make this site remember or not.

**Third Party Tracking Codes And Advertisements**

In addition with storing essential and preference based cookies, some advertisers or third party tracking codes (such as Google Analytics, Isocket or Google Adsense) also may store these cookies to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. You may view Google's privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) , Google Ads Privacy Policy by clicking [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and Isocket's policy [here](https://www.isocket.com/privacy/) respectively.

**Refusing Cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”. Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact upon the usability of this website and may spoil your browsing experience. Therefore, we do not recommend it, but you can opt for it.

**Securing Your Information**

We are committed to protect your personal privacy. Therefore, we will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Additionally we store all the personal information you provide in secured form.

**Juvenile Protection**

Children's privacy is most important to us. Therefore we don't collect any information or personal data from children below the age of 13. Additionally we also DO NOT allow registration of any members who are less than of 13 in age.

**Other Websites**

It should be noted that this website contains links to other websites and we are not responsible in any means for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Updating Privacy Policy**

We reserve right to change or update this privacy policy anytime by posting a new version on this website. Therefore, its your own duty to check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with and comply with all or any changes made.

**Contacting Us**

Your privacy is important to us. Hence, if there is any abuse or release of your personal data or information that is not meant to be public and is released by any of the site member, you can immediately contact us for the removal of same using the contact form by clicking [here](http://www.ubers.org/contact.php) by selecting subject as "Breach Of Privacy" and we would get back to you ASAP, rest assured. Also, you may contact us for any of the site related issues, as well.

In addition to all this, we strongly require you to read our disclaimer and legal liabilities and terms of acceptance, as well by clicking [here](http://www.ubers.org/misc.php?action=help&hid=12).

Some parts of this policy were taken from freelaw.net.
